You know there's always some growing
pains when a new person joins a team.
I remember nothing but
absolute delight when I came on board.
You may have heard that I was
up for the captain's chair.
Turns out you're stuck with me.
Nick Wagner. Your new captain.
[Morgan] Why are you being so cool,
right now? I hate this.
[Selena] I'm pissed.
It should have been me.
Root beer on an unprotected lip?
You're a madman.
The stress is getting to her.
She goes rogue and something happens...
She's not a cop.
[Morgan] You okay?
[Karadec] I told you it was a clean shot.
IA will clear me.
I'm not worried about your badge.
I'm worried about you.
[Nick] I just heard some rumors
you don't respond positively to authority.
Sometimes I forget what it's
like to have somebody looking out for me.
See you tomorrow, Gillory.
- [Morgan] Hey, any news?
- [Daphne] We found Roman.
- [Oz] I'm sending you a photo now.
- [Morgan] That's not Roman.
Roman asked me to put eyes on you and Ava,
just to make sure you two were okay.
[Ava] Actually let myself believe
that he didn't abandon us.
I still believe that.
Arthur, I want that backpack.
So, you think that
whatever's in that bag
will give you answers
and not just more questions?
[crackling]
[♪ "Hustle and Cuss" playing]
Huh. That's weird. You see that?
Hmm.
It's not coming back.
I'ma go check it out.
♪ Knock on the door
And the door knocks back ♪
♪ The joke never go no further than that ♪
All clear so far.
♪ Back down the stack ♪
♪ And we hustle and cuss
Lick on the dust ♪
♪ Hustle and cuss
[grunts]
Lick on the dust ♪
We good? What's your 20?
[alarm blaring]
♪ Hustle and cuss
And lick on the dust ♪
♪ You muscle and fuss ♪
♪ You muscle and fuss
And lick on the dust ♪
[coughing]
Base, we got a guard down.
♪ Hustle and cuss ♪
♪ You muscle and fuss ♪
[♪ song ends]
[alarm continues blaring]
[♪ "Not My Problem" playing]
♪ We all eight billion
Wah wah wah ♪
♪ Making plans and they
Nah nah nah ♪
[phone buzzing]
[♪ music stops]
- Good morning.
- Morgan, hey, hey. Are you and Ava okay?
Yeah, we're good. What's up?
I'ma ask you straight up.
You have somebody following me again?
What? No. What are you talking about?
I don't know. I think someone's been
on my tail the past few days.
Maybe it's nothing.
Arthur, if you feel like you might be
in danger, you should call the police.
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
Roman wasn't too keen
on the cops, remember?
What does this have to do with Roman?
That's what I'm trying to figure out here.
I mean... [sighs]
Were you able to learn anything about
what was inside that backpack of his?
No, not yet.
[sighs] All right, well, look, maybe
you should just hide the bag for now,
'cause whoever Roman's running from might
not want what's inside getting out.
You hear me?
Yeah. Hey, I gotta go, okay.
All right, well, look,
just be careful, all right, you and Ava.
Keep your head on a swivel.
You too.
Ava and I didn't glove up at home.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Only if you think you two might be
suspects in Roman's disappearance.
I think you can count us out.
And nothing in the bag look familiar?
- Rang any bells?
- No.
Also, Roman's not a huge fan
of law enforcement,
so if we could just keep this between us.
We'll keep the circle small.
- Thank you.
- [knocks on door]
What's going on?
Just revisiting an old case.
Call came in pretty high profile.
I want these two on it.
Go, I got this.
And close the door.
She only arrived here last week.
She have a name?
Young Girl Leaning On A Windowsill.
You guys are saying she a lot.
We are talking about a painting, right?
Painted by Rembrandt in 1645.
Up until last night, she was here
with our other Dutch masters.
"This intimate portrait captures the most
fleeting moments of human expression."
Sorry, I missed it.
We'll need a list of museum employees,
anyone with access.
Of course. Then I should call the Fosters,
so they hear it from me.
The Fosters?
Linda and Greg Foster
loaned us the Rembrandt.
Any idea how much it's worth?
I believe they paid over 20 million
at auction a few years ago.
- I'll get you that list.
- Thank you.
[Morgan scoffs] Uh,
we are Major Crimes, right?
I'm not really seeing
what's major about this.
A theft of major artwork carries
a penalty of up to 10 years
before the DA attacks on possession,
conspiracy, breaking and entering.
Why? You prefer a dead body?
No, I've just seen actual missing girls
get less attention.
Well, like it or not, every news outlet's
gonna run with this story tonight.
The captain's probably trying to keep
this thing from blowing up in our faces.
One guard said there was too much smoke
for her to get a look at the thief.
Second guard took a blow to the head,
but I hear should be okay.
So this is our point of entry?
[Daphne] Yeah, and exit
as far as we can tell.
We had whatever this is
sent over to the lab for testing.
Well, put a rush on the results
and see if we can get a log
- of visitors the past few weeks.
- Okay.
So the thief entered here, but
the Rembrandt's all the way over there.
Most thieves prefer not to bust
through the wall like the Kool-Aid Man.
[scoffs] Okay, so this person took
the time to cut out the window,
toss down a rope, slide down right here.
And then just walks right by Vermeer,
Caravaggio, Turner, Rubens, Delacroix,
and Goya? Do you have any idea
how much all of those are worth?
I'm sure you're going to tell me.
A lot more than the Rembrandt.
If this heist was about money,
the thief would have taken
the most valuable piece he could.
[cash register dings]
[Morgan] Our guy would have known
that this Goya was the real jackpot.
- [cash register dings]
- Maybe they didn't do their research.
Every single detail
of this thing was planned.
I mean, look at the frame, that perfectly
straight line down the inside seam.
Removing this canvas
took precision and time.
Somebody wanted this painting
for a reason.
Whoever the thief was,
they were not in it for the money.
This was personal.
They wanted her.
Did you say 22 million?
Yeah, but if Morgan's right, we need
to find out more about the Rembrandt
to figure out who might have taken it.
And what their real motivation was.
[♪ "Count Your Blessings" playing]
Excuse me.
Is this Major Crimes?
You must be Mr. Eastman.
I'm Captain Wagner, we spoke on the phone.
Of course, please, call me Rhys.
Rhys flew in from Mexico City this morning
to help us find our missing girl.
Yeah, I had a lead on Kahlo's
La Mesa Herida, but... it didn't pan out.
Uh, help us how?
I'm an art recovery specialist.
I recover lost, missing, or stolen art.
They cram all the info right there
in the title, huh? That's helpful.
- And you are?
- Gillory works with us as a consultant.
She does, and she really feels as
though this painting has enough attention
without flying someone in.
[Karadec] Did the Fosters send you?
No, the insurance company did.
If I can recover the Rembrandt safely,
the insurance company
can avoid cutting a rather large check.
Oh, good, good. What a relief.
Okay, so this entire investigation is
about saving an insurance company money.
That's awesome, right guys? Just wanted
to make sure you guys heard that. Go on.
Morgan believes that the Fosters'
Rembrandt was targeted
for a reason other than money.
[chuckles]
I mean, anything's possible,
but in my experience,
- it's always about money.
- [Morgan] Mmm.
Well, not this time.
I mean, thieves don't steal masterpieces
to hang on their walls, Ms. Gillory.
Maybe this one did, Mr. Eastman.
[Karadec] Morgan and I'll go see
what the Fosters
can tell us about their painting.
Great. Fill in Rhys on the way.
Shall we?
The moment we saw her at auction,
we knew we had to have her.
I mean... [chuckles] ...honestly,
we would have paid even more.
We think she's priceless.
Greg and I started a hedge fund
right out of college.
We worked 80 hours a week
for decades.
So by the time we even thought about kids,
we couldn't imagine chasing a baby
around here, making a mess.
So, we often thought of the girl
in that painting as our daughter.
Can you think of anyone
who may have wanted to steal from you?
[Greg] No. You think this was personal?
- So, why share her?
- I'm sorry, what?
Mmm. Oh, just you're talking about
this painting like your daughter,
and I've never put my daughter
in a museum.
I'm just wondering
why you wouldn't keep it to yourself.
Loaning out a masterpiece increases
its visibility and its reputation.
And its value. Spend some time
in a museum, jacks up the price.
You can sell it to the highest bidder.
- She's not for sale.
- Mmm.
[Rhys] Well, in my experience,
thieves are two things.
They're greedy and chatty.
And these masterpieces,
they don't fetch the same price on
the black market as they do at an auction.
So these thieves,
they like to talk to people.
They ask around and all it will take
is one of these people to call me
and I can help negotiate
the return of your lovely servant girl.
Do you call her a servant girl?
It's not a servant.
Excuse me?
She's leaning out the windowsill looking
for business. That's a working girl.
Well, there's speculation
that the subject was a courtesan,
but widely believed
that she was either a servant girl--
A servant girl with a gold braid?
Come on. [chuckles]
Look at the way she leans.
It's domestic, not provocative.
It's upsetting, is what it is, because
she looks like a child, but she's working.
She's contemplating life.
- I-Is this important to the investigation?
- No, it's not.
What else can you tell us
about the Rembrandt itself?
The details about her providence,
they're all in here.
This girl in the window's traveled
all over the world.
Paris, London, Berlin. She's lived
a much more exciting life than me.
Except now she's probably rolled up
in the back of somebody's van.
Well, let's hope she got it all
out of her system first.
- This is interesting.
- You got something?
Maybe. Right after Rembrandt painted
the young girl in 1645, he sold it.
At that point, it sort of bounced around
for a few 100 years,
17th century Paris,
kind of skimmed this part,
until it was purchased by a Prussian
nobleman who kept it until he died.
[coughs]
Then his family kept it till 1932
until Franz von Papen
dissolved the Free State of Prussia.
I thought you said this was interesting.
Look, I'm trying to care
about this case, okay?
Which at the moment is just saving an
insurance company from having to pay money
to a couple of people
who seem to be doing just fine.
Where did she go next?
To a Polish businessman in Kraków,
and he hung it in his family home.
Then it just kind of bounced around
from collection to collection
until good old Greg
and Linda paid a fortune for it.
Why is any of this important?
I don't know yet.
Lab results came back on those slags
we found on the museum floor,
tested positive for aluminum oxide,
so I did some research.
When aluminum combines with ferric oxide,
it creates a thermite reaction
hot enough to melt glass.
[Karadec] That would explain why we didn't
find any glass shards under the sky light.
It also came up in a report
on another museum heist.
Two years ago, a Matisse was stolen
from the Kunsthal Museum in Rotterdam.
And aluminum oxide was found
under the museum sky light.
Which might mean
this isn't our thief's first rodeo.
You and Daphne look for others.
So far we found 19 heists around the world
with the same MO.
Always a masterpiece stolen from
a gallery. Always worth 10 to 30 million.
And traces of aluminum oxide
at every scene
under a window
or a skylight just like ours.
We have any idea who it might be?
Well, the internet seems to think so.
Some call him Jean-Baptiste.
- He's French?
- No, but the first painting he stole was.
"The White Duck by Jean-Baptiste Oudrey."
Stolen in Paris, 12 years ago.
Tell me somebody's got eyes on him.
Only once.
[Karadec] He tried to steal a Picasso
in Madrid five years ago,
but a guard shot him in the left shoulder,
and he fled empty handed.
- Okay, so why can't anybody find this guy?
- [Rhys] Because he might not exist.
- He could be a myth.
- What do you mean?
I mean, it's impressive work,
but the name Jean-Baptiste comes up
whenever there's a heist unsolved,
the thief got in and out without a trace,
escaped with another masterpiece.
Must be Jean-Baptiste.
But is he real? Maybe.
It could be ten different guys.
Check this out. I searched public records.
Someone sued claiming
to be the Rembrandt's rightful owner.
We have a name?
Yeah, an Ari Weisman,
but it looks like the records are sealed.
Ari would be the first guy to take matters
into his own hands
- when the court ruled against him.
- [Nick] We got an address?
Yeah, looks like he's local.
Captain, I could use a hand from
Detectives Ozdil and Forrester for a bit.
Is this about that cold case?
It is.
You heard the lieutenant?
Can I help with anything?
No, I'm good. I'll keep you posted.
Why don't you guys go find out
if this Ari Weisman responds
to the name Jean-Baptiste?
[Ari] We just wanted the painting back.
How badly?
Enough to sue, not steal.
Sorry, you think
that painting belonged to you?
Not me, my grandma.
My father bought that painting in 1932.
I remember the day he hang it up
on the wall.
Whenever we all got together,
there was the girl smiling down to us.
Always felt she felt
like part of the family.
- [chuckles]
- [Rhys] Your father had wonderful taste.
It's a very special piece.
One of my favorites.
We lived in Kraków.
My father, my mother, and my two brothers,
Jacob and Samuel.
I was the youngest.
The only one in our family that survived.
When the Nazis came...
they took everything.
I'm so sorry.
We're still here.
I'm guessing you searched
the auction catalogs for years.
I thought she'd never find it, and
then one day there it was, up for sale.
The owners.
They wanted to sell it to us. [grunts]
For $20 million.
We don't have $20 million.
The court said
we couldn't prove it was stolen.
Is that all?
Actually, Ari, we have to ask,
where were you last night?
I was here with my grandma.
I saw your name
on the museum visitor logs.
You were there a couple of days ago.
I wanted to take a photo to show to her.
Have you traveled
outside the country the last few years?
No.
No, but she keeps asking me
to take her to Poland.
She wants to visit
the house where she grew up.
She's not doing much traveling now.
That painting was the closest
she'll come to going home.
Please.
Thank you.
[Selena] Thanks for the assist, you guys.
Once every item is tagged, photographed,
and packaged for forensics--
I'll get TID to get started
on data extraction on his phone.
Hopefully, we uncover
text messages, call logs.
You want fiber analysis on the backpack?
All of it. I want the works.
This much activity,
people gonna start asking questions.
What are we saying
if the captain asks what we're doing?
Tell him to talk to me.
And let's run this stack of photos
through facial recognition.
Okay.
Okay, let's go over it one last time.
- Mom, I got it. Trust me.
- I do trust you.
That's why I'm paying you a premium
instead of hiring a babysitter.
You've literally rejected
every babysitter in California.
And I wouldn't say
you're paying me a premium.
It is a perfectly reasonable wage
based on current market conditions.
Listen, Chloe's routine has changed
since she's down a nap.
So can you just indulge me?
[sighs] Nap time from one to three.
Classical music on low.
For lunch, she gets half a grilled cheese
and mushed up zucchini.
After that, she can play with her blocks,
and if she gets frustrated,
then distract her
with the singing giraffe.
- I wanna be very clear about something.
- Hmm.
She's gonna get frustrated
and she will throw those blocks.
- I'll be prepared.
- Okay, perfect.
Oh, wait, Mom. Hold on a sec.
Can this wait? I got to go.
I know,
but I just wanted to know what the cops
are doing with Dad's stuff from his bag.
Did they find anything yet? [scoffs]
These things take time.
I know, but can't you push them
to make it go faster?
- Can't you be patient, please?
- [sighs]
Listen, there's a reason
I gave his stuff to them, okay?
They're gonna find something
and when they do,
I'll let you know, I promise.
- Okay.
- All right. Thank you.
Also, I'm pretty sure that singing giraffe
is broken, so best of luck to you. Bye.
- Is it really? No, Mom.
- Love you.
[sighs]
And what is your job at the museum?
I'm a gallery attendant.
I've been the assistant curator
at The Harbach for almost twenty years.
I just collect tickets and the paycheck.
I don't know anything
about that painting getting stolen.
Did you notice anything
out of the ordinary the past few weeks?
Maybe a visitor lingering around.
Mmm. One sneezed on a Vermeer last week,
so I showed him Caravaggio's
Judith Beheading Holofernes as a warning.
How'd you get that bruise on your face?
Took a nap on the floor.
Hmm.
Are you sure you haven't seen
anything out of the ordinary?
I noticed a guy hanging
around the Rembrandt a few days ago.
He looked familiar,
like I'd see him a few times,
but I mean, we see a lot of faces.
Do you remember anything
specific about him?
I remember thinking,
he looked like he went for a run.
Yeah, that's him.
[footsteps approaching]
Oh, come on.
We have to consider Ari a suspect.
He has means, motive, and his alibi wants
the Rembrandt just as much as he does.
Yeah, because the painting
belongs to her. Am I right?
I don't disagree, but--
No, but nothing.
Listen, the Weismans are
the victims here, not the suspects.
Are you picturing Miriam Weisman
rappelling through a skylight?
Well, Ari's a gymnast.
I can totally picture him doing it.
Look, all the museum employees
that we've talked to so far have alibis.
Morgan, what are you doing?
I am fixing our crime board
and correcting the timeline to include
the first time
that the painting was stolen.
In 1939.
Well, why confine ourselves
to solving crimes in the 21st century?
If we find The Young Girl,
we should be returning it
to Miriam Weisman,
- not the Fosters.
- [phone buzzes]
I got to take this.
Morgan, it's not that simple.
I don't know what to tell you.
There's gotta be something we can do.
Well, even if we had the jurisdiction
to resolve a crime from 80 years ago,
it's just not how the system works.
I really wish there was more we could do.
[Karadec sighs]
Who was that?
Excuse me?
You said that thieves love
to talk to people
and sometimes those people call you.
Was that people calling?
A man called.
Claims he knows where the painting is.
He wants to meet with me to discuss.
Where?
- [scoffs]
- You don't wanna tell me
'cause you're worried if the police
get involved, they're gonna ruin it?
If we spook whoever this guy is,
we may never recover the painting.
- Fine, then I'm coming with you.
- I can't show up with the cops.
I don't see any cops, do you?
Where is this guy?
He's late.
And why exactly is he calling you?
Well, not to sound insufferable, but
I'm the only person that does what I do.
[chuckles]
Sorry, you were trying
to not sound insufferable?
Well, from what I gather, you're the only
person that does what you do too.
It's a little different, but sure.
[Rhys sighs]
Well, I think we have some time to spare.
Let's see how this guy got in.
- Knock yourself out.
- Come on, you're coming with me.
I need your insufferable talents
on that roof.
[♪ "Count Your Blessings" playing]
[♪ music stops]
If I could just... Hello.
Lieutenant, you got a second?
Good news only.
Well, TID is backed up.
Hobson says cracking
that BlackBerry could take weeks,
too many phones, not enough texts.
Remind her of the parking ticket
I got her mother out of
in front of the Van Nuys courthouse.
She owes me.
You know the difference
between good news and bad?
I ran those photos in the backpack
through facial recognition.
No criminal record
on the ones we could match
parking tickets, traffic stops,
nothing major.
- And the ones we couldn't match?
- Only one.
All right, I'll take it from here.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Did you know there's
a German diaper derby competition?
It's held annually in Bavaria.
Contestants are judged
on speed, efficiency,
and the artistic flourish
of the diaper application.
- I do well.
- Is Chloe napping or not?
Yes, which brings me to my next point.
Since I'm helping you babysit
and not being babysat...
I'll give you 10% of my pay.
Fine, 20%.
Deal.
And I won't tell Mom
you're going through her clothes.
How generous of you.
What if we promise not to touch anything?
That works for me.
[Rhys] Have you ever stolen anything?
Nothing with a provenance, you?
Yes, stole a classmate's trainers
once in primary school.
- Scotland Yard know about this?
- [chuckles]
He deserved it.
Used to kick this kid, Gideon,
in the shins with those shoes at recess.
Well, did you wear them to school?
No, I donated them to a thrift store
right by the bus stop.
That way he could see them
every time he looked through the window.
You monster.
- This glass is reflective.
- What do you mean?
These skylights all have
a one-way window film on them.
The thief wouldn't be able to see in.
It's a risky little game, breaking glass,
not knowing who's down there.
[museum director] Excuse me.
We were just leaving.
The guard saw you come up here.
Are you Mr. Eastman?
Yeah, why?
One of my docents found this at the front.
They didn't see who left it.
So you go back to the crime scene
on your own without a police escort?
Well, yeah--
Detective Karadec,
did you know about this?
Know about what, sir?
The museum director just called me and
told me that your partner took Mr. Eastman
on a tour of the crime scene.
- That's...
- Ducked right under the tape,
and cut the seal.
Are you trying to sabotage
this investigation?
You made it quite clear
how you feel about this case.
No, I'm not trying to sabotage anything,
okay? I was trying to help.
He was going anyway. Would you prefer
I just let him go by himself?
Neither of you should've been there
in the first place.
Okay, I understand that. And I'm sorry.
But if we didn't,
we wouldn't have gotten this.
Whoever left this wants
to meet at 1:00 p.m.
That gives us less than 2 hours.
Are Forrester and Ozdil still
with the lieutenant?
You thinking a surveillance up?
Yes, and we need to see
the museum's security cameras.
Maybe we can get eyes
on whoever dropped this off.
Don't you think that Rhys should take
the lead on this though?
- And why would we do that?
- Because I'm who they want to speak to.
Great idea. I'll send Morgan with you
and you can tamper with more evidence.
Hey, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry I went to a building
without your permission first.
- I see now that that was a bad idea.
- Bad idea?
How about reckless and insubordinate?
I just said I'm sorry.
I know that you don't like rules,
but when you're in my precinct,
I expect you to follow my command.
You practice that in a mirror?
- Morgan, calm--
- Do not tell me to calm down.
We need to grab someone from the SIS.
The sooner that we get
to the ransom's location,
the sooner that we can start surveillance.
- Okay, great. Rhys and I will follow you.
- No.
Detective Karadec and I can handle it
from here.
Our consultants have done enough.
- Are you kicking me off the case?
- [phone vibrates]
I walked up on a roof!
Oh, great. The Fosters
are on their way up. They want an update.
Talk to them. I'll be waiting downstairs.
Just make it quick.
What is going on?
Morgan, what were you thinking?
I get it!
This is why I work alone.
Do you drink alone?
- I prefer to have company.
- Great.
Good luck.
You believe that guy?
Kicking me off the case
so he can go follow a lead that we found.
He knows how I work. I do my thing
and then cases get solved, right?
What's wrong with that?
Nothing's wrong with that, Rhys.
That's the answer to that question.
You have every right to be upset.
Yeah, I know I do
because he called me out like I'm a child.
I have kids,
I don't even talk to them like that.
What?
Boys, girls, mix?
Mix. Don't change the subject.
I gotta get this out.
And why are we still driving?
Shouldn't we be
eating and drinking by now?
Are you suggesting I go faster?
Look at the car you're driving.
We just got passed by a Subaru.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Where did you get this?
Our consultants came across it.
Good news is your painting
doesn't appear to be damaged.
What happens now?
We're supposed to pay the ransom?
That's not what I said, sir.
The LAPD never pays ransom.
We don't suggest that you do either.
I don't believe this.
So what do you suggest that we do?
Are we just gonna sit here and do nothing?
Detective, we have been waiting
by the phone,
and we have heard nothing, and now this?
Who sent you this?
Do you have any leads? Anything?
We're assembling a team to follow
that lead and recover your painting.
And how long does it take
to assemble this team of yours?
They're assembling
in the war room right now,
and I should be with them instead of here.
Detective, we just want her back.
I understand, sir.
Let us handle the response.
We'll get back to you
when we find out more.
Thank you
for keeping us informed, Detective.
Of course.
- Just a little bit more.
- Yes, sir.
- [phone buzzing]
- Thanks, bro.
- This is Arthur.
- Hi, this is Ava Sinquerra.
Boss, you want us to--
[Ava] Hello?
Um...
I just wanted to call you because there's
something I didn't get an answer to
at the diner 'cause my mom flipped out.
[chuckles]
Well, how does your mom feel
about you calling me?
Oh, this call never happened. [chuckles]
Actually, I should probably tell her
so she won't ground me again.
Yeah, well, it sounds like a wise move.
Look, Ava, I'm in the middle of working
right now, so--
You said that I reminded you of my dad?
What was he like?
[sighs]
Hello?
Look, I won't bother you again.
I promise. I just...
I'm sorry. Maybe this wasn't such
a good idea. I'll just leave you alone.
No, no, just hold on a second.
If you wanna have a serious talk
about your dad,
then we have to do it the right way.
I don't know, maybe me, you,
and your mom, we could...
I don't know. Find ourselves back
at that diner at some point.
How does that sound to you?
Sure, yeah.
Listen, Ava, until that happens,
you and I, we can't...
[sighs]
Look, Roman didn't always do things
the easy way,
but he always did things the right way.
I mean, he had a lot to do with me
getting my life together
and believe me,
he saved my ass more than once.
He's a stand-up guy through and through.
Well, look, Ava,
I gotta get back to work here.
- Hey, Arthur.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Of course, sweetheart.
Everything all right, Detective?
Something on your mind?
You know, I read somewhere carrying
around unexpressed frustrations is like
carrying a heavy backpack.
Every unspoken thought adds
another stone to the load,
making your journey much more difficult.
- She's confused, sir.
- Hmm.
Yeah, so am I.
You're confused?
Sir, is there something you wanna tell me?
I can't protect you
if I don't know where you are.
I have to be in a position to help
if things go south.
I need to know everything,
and that's not because I don't trust her,
but because I do.
Still confused?
No.
Good. Because the same applies
to you and everyone else. You understand?
Yes, sir.
Next time you lose your cool with her.
I'd suggest you find a different approach.
Oh, yeah. Why is that?
Because if you don't,
it's gonna put me and you in a position
where things will definitely go south.
All clear.
Just getting a little impatient.
Don't worry.
The ransomer will turn up soon.
With you, Detective.
Impatient with me. Why?
We're sitting here nice and quiet.
Nothing but time for you to read me in.
Read you in on what?
Roman Sinquerra.
Come on, Adam.
You don't think I see things?
What do you wanna know?
[alarm blaring]
Oh. We don't have time for this.
It'll blow our cover.
Or spook our ransomer.
[Nick] We're here for the painting,
not some car thief.
Leave it alone.
He's committing a crime. I...
I'll handle this.
Detective.
Hey! Hey, man, that's my car.
What are you doing?
Bro, get out of my car now.
Whoa! LAPD, put the gun down.
Now. At your feet. Let's go.
Put that gun down now.
Drop it. On the ground.
Good. Keep your hands
where I can see 'em, son.
[tires screeching]
Hey, that's our guy. Let's go!
Hey! Hey!
Move!
- Wait, so now you're stealing the car.
- That's right. It's your lucky day.
[siren wailing]
[phone buzzing]
- Detective.
- [Karadec] You took my car, sir.
Yeah, I couldn't wait.
He was getting away.
[tires screech]
Well, I'm right behind you.
What? You stole that car?
No, sir. I commandeered a private vehicle
in an emergency because you left me.
I had no choice.
I told you not to mess with that guy.
He was committing a crime!
Get out of that car, Detective.
You hear me?
Yes, I hear you, sir.
Pull over right now!
Pull to the side of the road.
Need some help?
I got it handled.
[horn honks]
- That was close.
- I'm well aware!
I'm gonna make my move!
What move? No move!
[horns honking]
Let's pull a two-vehicle box-in.
Just pull over and get
a chopper in the air.
We need eyes in the sky.
Just listen to me, Detective!
[grunts]
Had we both been in one car,
I think that we...
Never mind.
[horns honking]
[Morgan] I'm not even convinced
he should have the job.
I mean, Lieutenant Solo was
absolutely qualified.
Well, how did he get the promotion?
Politics, nepotism, I guess.
You know what it might be? He's tall.
Data shows taller people
get promoted faster. Did you know that?
But if you can't buy pants off the rack,
what's the point of living?
[chuckles] Okay. When's the last time
you bought pants off a rack?
Pretty sure there's a tailor in London
who's got your inseam memorized.
Well, you know,
I do like clothes that fit.
Mm-hmm, I can tell.
You think you know me? But you can't get
past the accent, can you?
I mean, you do sound like you were born
clutching a croquet mallet.
[Rhys laughs]
Well, let me share something with you.
My father, he was a bin man.
Always out collecting
other people's rubbish.
All the kids at school,
they used to make fun of me.
They said that they could smell it on me,
but when I walked into a museum,
I was staring up at the same beauty
as kings and queens,
like, this kid from Stevenage.
It didn't matter who I was.
I mean, The Mona Lisa smiled at me
like she smiled at everyone.
Mmm.
I'm gonna be honest, I'm still really
pissed, so I wasn't fully listening,
but I did hear bin man and Mona Lisa.
Not exactly sure how they're connected,
but I bet it was poignant.
- [sighs] It was.
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, I'm glad you didn't hear it.
- Mmm?
You don't strike me
as a girl that's attracted to someone
that's so sentimental anyway.
Hmm. What am I attracted to?
I think you appreciate a challenge.
I think you need something exciting enough
to get you out of that head of yours.
Really?
Like what?
I have a few ideas.
[♪ "Walk of Fame" playing]
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Every night, it's all the same ♪
♪ Hungry cries are calling out my name ♪
♪ Ooh yeah, it's a walk of fame ♪
♪ And through the tears
I can see it so clear ♪
♪ Walk away, walk away ♪
[♪ music stops]
[Karadec] He tried to steal a Picasso
in Madrid five years ago.
The guard shot him in the left shoulder,
and he fled empty-handed.
[Rhys] I'm the only person
that does what I do.
[Daphne] Nineteen heists around the world
with the same MO.
[Karadec] This isn't
our thief's first rodeo.
[Rhys] In my experience,
it's always about money.
Have you ever stolen anything?
Jean-Baptiste might not exist.
It could be a myth. It's a very
special piece, one of my favorites.
[phone buzzes]
I should get that.
Hey, what's up?
I'm down at the museum,
and you're gonna wanna see this.
[♪ music resumes]
Our case just got blown wide open.
♪ And through the tears
I can see it so clear ♪
♪ Walk away, walk away ♪
♪ Yeah, every time I walk
It's a walk of fame ♪
♪ Ooh yeah, it's a walk of fame ♪
♪ And through the mirror
I can see it so clear ♪
♪ You walk away, walk away ♪
♪ Yeah, every time I walk
It's a walk of fame ♪
♪ I walk the concrete ♪
Who are you?
[♪ song ends]
[screams]
Where is it?
I want that backpack.