We got to get the bourbon going,
and we got to get our booze
delivered off-board
until we get our license back.
[Goodie]
We distribute the way they did
back during Prohibition.
* exciting, intense music *
-There will be blowback, sir.
-Fix it. You fix it.
-There will be blowback!
-You fix it.
Do you want to make me proud?
Yeah.
Then you got to finish this.
That guy-- he, um...
did he ever come back around?
-No.
-Good.
I did something right.
Let's talk about
this booze thing.
I want a share.
[Dwight]
See, everything you fucking take
that's not yours,
you take and you take
like a fucking animal.
If I want to get to you
or anybody,
it's done, and don't you ever
fucking forget that.
-[gun cocks]
-Down!
-[gunfire]
-[patrons screaming]
[Quiet Ray]
You fucking cocksucker.
-You're dead!
-That was meant for me!
* exciting, intense music *
[buzzing]
* low, tense music *
All that was meant for me.
So what are you saying?
-You saw this coming?
-[Dwight] No.
Why would I put you
in that kind of situation?
What sense does that make?
It makes no sense.
So let me tell you something.
It's been a long time
since someone
tried to whack me.
Accidentally.
"Accidentally."
You know,
no matter how you word it,
it still leads to death.
What do you expect me to say?
I expect you to shut up
and listen.
I sat down with you
and tried to talk,
and what do you do?
You accuse me of-of-of
whacking what's-his-name?
You know his name, Ray.
Look, I don't give a fuck
what his name is.
The fact is,
you brought that prick up
and it fucked the negotiating.
[Dwight]
Demanding 80%
or else?
That's not a negotiation.
[Quiet Ray] Look, what do you
want from me, anyway?
[Dwight] I want to finish
the business we started.
I want to cut you in on this
-liquor concern, you know?
-Cut me in?
You sound like you're giving me
a Christmas gift or something.
This is something
that you should just do.
Hey, this is gonna pay off
for both of us.
Yeah? How's that?
Look, I want to get
into the clubs,
the hotels, retailers,
which means I need access
to the Northeast.
And whatever pull you have
in Atlantic City, Las Vegas--
And what about our deal?
I can't. It's out of
the fucking question.
Come on. There's enough
to go around for all of us,
for-for Christ's sake.
You got to be reasonable.
You got some
fucking balls on you,
you know that?
All right, we'll put off
the deal for another day,
but let me tell you something
right now.
That day is gonna come,
and it's gonna come very soon,
you understand me?
Yeah, I understand.
Good.
All right.
I'll help you.
[phone beeps]
What'd he say?
Eh, not that much.
He didn't discuss numbers
or terms or anything like that.
He's gonna whack me.
Matter of time.
Dunmire's after you as well.
Masked or not, disguised or not,
we know it was them
in Hot Springs.
So what's the play?
First thing you got to do
is get that seal
off the distillery.
That's a priority.
How we gonna do that?
Some people need a wake-up call.
* tense music *
* percussive, upbeat music *
***
[Dwight chuckles]
You seem to be lost in thought.
Are you kind of thinking
about something here?
Well, Tyson...
is he not driving you anymore?
Uh, well, sometimes.
Yeah. He's trying
to broaden his horizons.
Listen, he wants to be
an earner.
That's understandable.
Sure. Why not?
And you...
Mr. Chuckles,
are you happy with your job?
Too happy.
[chuckles]
-[Bigfoot] This close enough?
-Yeah, it's close enough.
* upbeat music *
Let's do this.
No. Wait, wait, wait.
You stay here.
I got to be discreet.
-In that suit?
-Yeah.
Hey, boss.
They got metal detectors.
Fuck.
-Come on, come on.
-Here.
See?
All right.
[phone camera clicks]
[beeps]
-[alarm blares]
-Ooh, ooh.
Can I get you to come
right here, sir?
-Mm-hmm.
-Turn around for me, please.
Must be the brass balls.
[chuckles]
[wand whining]
You want to remove
your belt buckle, sir?
It's kind of small.
-Yeah.
-It's like a house pet.
[laughs]
* atmospheric music *
[Dwight]
"Lawman of the Year."
[chuckles]
[mutters]
Mr. Manfredi.
[Dwight]
How are you?
Uh, whatever is
discussed here today
will be held
in the strictest confidence.
Always.
There's no shame in crying uncle
when all the odds are stacked
against you.
Is that an insult,
Attorney General?
No.
Look... [chuckles]
Jeremiah Dunmire...
I mean, you're-you're not naive.
Now, he's a force of nature
round here,
round these parts.
So, what, um...
what message would you like me
to pass along?
I'd like you to listen to me
very carefully.
You're in power
because of that crazy bastard.
That crazy bastard's in power
because of who resides
in the governor's mansion.
But that won't be for long.
It won't? [chuckles]
Well, that's news to me.
You know,
I'm gonna build you a path.
A path built on trust.
But I'm gonna need
one small favor.
I'm gonna need
your friends down at
the Alcoholic Beverage
Law Enforcement Commission
to restore my sister's
liquor license,
which was taken away
without any real reason.
And if you do that,
I'm gonna be in debt to you,
and that's a good thing to have,
a good chip to have.
Because I can do things
that other people can't
or just won't.
It's time for you to leave, sir.
The first time
I arrive somewhere,
I try to make
the most favorable presentation.
The second...
not so much.
* low, tense music *
You have no idea
who this man is.
I know exactly who he is.
Exactly.
This is very nice.
Lawman of the Year.
Good day, Mr. Manfredi.
It's a little early to tell.
[door closes]
What's wrong?
He won't talk to me.
My old man.
You're lucky I'm talking to you.
After what you did
at the distillery.
I know.
I do things for him
I know are wrong,
but I do 'em anyway.
Fuck.
There's something else I did
that went wrong.
What did you do?
I don't want to say something
that'll push you away.
Do you know what would happen
if they all knew
I was here with you right now?
I know.
And I'm sorry.
* somber music *
No, I just...
I really like you.
And when I'm with you, I...
What do you want to say, Cole?
I feel like
everything's gonna be okay.
And I don't want
to fuck that up.
-[pop music playing quietly]
-[door opens]
[Tyson] Yo, I got to ask you
a question, man.
What was your first hustle?
Stolen newspapers.
I sold 'em on the F train.
Think I was eight.
No, man, no.
I'm talking about
as a grown man now.
Like, what did you do
when you first
got to get into it?
I shook down a guy
who owned a shoe store.
Easy money.
[laughs] You shook down...
That's a cold motherfucker
right there.
Hey, look, man,
it ain't rocket science.
All right? It's all about
supply and demand.
What do people demand,
and how could you supply it?
-That's it.
-Yeah.
You could become a cop.
[laughs] Fuck out of here, man.
No. Damn. What's going on?
Fake cop.
-Fake cop.
-Right?
You steal from bad guys
and give to good guys.
Like fucking Robin Hood.
I like that.
I used to raid a joint,
rob 'em blind, clear them out.
They couldn't call it in.
-They couldn't report it.
-What?
Real drug deal--
Real kingpins and shit?
Back in the day, yeah. But you
stick to people your own age,
-these college kids.
-Mm.
What are they into?
These kids are
crazy as fuck, man.
You know, they like Molly,
Xan, Perc, um...
I don't know, man. It's been
a minute since my campus days,
-to be honest with you.
-There's a market there.
-It's good, so...
-It is, yeah.
There's a market there.
Here come my little
college connection right here.
You onto something.
Hey, Spencer.
[clears throat] Got a little
business proposition for you.
-Is that a fact?
-Yeah, it's fact.
Come here. Let me holla at you.
[phone buzzing]
-Hey.
-[Dwight] Hey, Margaret.
Do you know anyone in
the attorney general's office?
Uh, I know him socially.
-I know his wife.
-Christ, really?
Is there anyone you don't know?
I could use a political favor.
Yeah.
So what's in it for me?
Ah.
What kind of guy
do you think I am, huh?
I scratch your back,
you scratch mine.
Don't we already
do that for free?
Guess that's true.
[Spencer]
All right, pull over here.
[engine shuts off]
This frat,
they supply most of the campus
-and a lot of Tulsa.
-[Tyson] You sure?
A hundred percent.
I party with them.
Trust-fund kids.
Oil-money douchebags
who love rolling on E.
This is the spot.
Sounds promising.
Yo, let's bust a move.
[clears throat]
Easy, cowboy.
We got to do recon.
The fuck are you talking about?
I-- My ass is on the line
with Dwight, bro.
Come on, man,
don't got no time for this
"Oh, this is what
the boss wants"-ass bullshit.
When you paint a room,
-you got to do...
-Oh, my...
-...your prep work first.
-[groans] Here he goes
with this shit.
-How 'bout I do it?
-I don't know.
What experience
do you have, uh--
Getting into frat houses?
[Tyson chuckling]
More than anyone here.
[Goodie]
All right.
Tomorrow, then.
Tomorrow? How 'bout right now?
Easy. I got to get the badges.
And I'm gonna need to know
the number of guys in there,
how to get into the basement
and if there's a guard dog.
That last one is very,
very important.
-[piano music plays quietly]
-[indistinct chatter]
-Margaret. [chuckles]
-Hi.
-It's been a minute, huh?
-I know.
-Mm.
-Ah.
Oh, it's so lovely to see you.
Great to see you, too, Anna.
And thank you for coming
all the way out here.
Oh, you didn't have
to twist my arm.
I love this place.
The people-watching alone
is worth it.
Thank you.
Lot of people prancing
around here-- ooh--
like they're somebody important.
[laughs]
Well, most of them are.
At least in Tulsa.
The hubby keeps saying
that we're gonna apply
for membership,
but like they say,
if I had a dime
for every broken promise...
Well, it is pricey.
-I'll give you that.
-Yeah.
Well, he's a public servant now,
so there's no more
law firm perks and bonuses.
Yeah, but, Anna...
attorney general?
Come on. That's a stepping stone
towards higher office, right?
[chuckles]
Yes. Maybe.
Well, I don't know.
Higher office, higher scrutiny.
You don't like the spotlight.
No, I actually don't mind that.
[both laugh]
It's just...
You know, other things.
Do you want to get a drink?
'Cause I could sure use one.
-Or two.
-[laughs]
And, Anna...
anything we talk about today,
you know me.
I'm a vault.
[phone buzzing]
[rock music playing quietly]
Hello.
Her marriage has problems,
and she's explaining them to me.
At length.
Well, let's hear it.
That's good.
You know,
you're pretty good at this.
I think you'd be a natural
as a spy.
Thresher owes you big-time.
So do I.
* mysterious music *
[vehicle door closes]
[Dwight]
There she is.
[Thresher over TV] ...stand up
for real Oklahomans...
[Dwight] I didn't know
you had cartoons here.
[laughs] Oh.
-Can I get you a water?
-Nah, I'm good. Thank you.
All right, let's do this fast.
[Dwight]
Listen, we could have met you
-at your house.
-Oh, yeah.
You'd blend right in.
Look,
I don't put anything
past Dunmire
and his puppet incumbent.
We're moving up,
and they're getting agitated.
I went to see the AG.
He wasn't buying my deal.
He does realize
that's his problem, right?
Dwight, I told you:
the Sicilian hustle
doesn't work down here.
You don't know
the political culture of Tulsa.
They just like working
with their own.
Why do you think I'm here?
Why rock the boat,
for shit's sake? Right?
[stammers] You can bust my balls
as soon as I get elected.
Can you believe
how fucking rude this guy is?
Let me explain something.
Do you remember
we had a conversation that
we'd pick up where we left off?
[Thresher]
Exactly. Dwight,
my polling is up.
My Q scores among likely voters
has doubled.
I got a real shot at this thing,
so why would I risk it all
to curry favor with some AG
on your behalf?
-Margaret.
-Then do it on your behalf.
Make it about you.
Building relationships.
Relation--
He's Dunmire's guy,
and you both know that.
Yeah, but he's also
the governor's guy.
And if you can pull
the AG away from the governor,
which I think you can,
maybe even get him
to endorse you...
-[Dwight] Mm-hmm.
-...that would be a coup.
And yeah,
your numbers are improving,
but a move like that
could put you over the top.
[Dwight]
Win one for yourself.
Man, you got to strike
while the iron is hot,
-am I right?
-[Margaret] Right.
Have a meeting for you.
Matter of fact, have a fucking
meeting at my place.
-It might bring you luck.
-At your place?
I mean, not the most enchanting
place to win a guy's favor.
[Margaret]
I think Bred-2-Buck's perfect.
Sets the right tone.
Yes.
Cal Thresher, billionaire,
but also...
man of the people.
Oh, now you're pushing it.
[Dwight]
No.
That's what I do, Cal.
Hey, let's shake.
Before I break it.
[Tyson]
You think she good in there?
Yeah, what, are they gonna
force her to do a keg stand?
-You got the badges, right?
-Of course.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
How you come up on this, bro?
-I know a motivated seller.
-Hell yeah.
They-they-they look
real as fuck.
Of course they are.
[Tyson]
Oh, here she comes, right here.
What's the word?
Six guys in the common area
playing Xbox.
A couple looked high, the other
two just looked pretty lame.
Basement is past the kitchen
on the left.
-No dog.
-Good.
-You finally ready to do this?
-Yes.
-Let's do it.
-I want to go with you.
-Wh-What? No way.
You did your part. This is ours.
* tense, percussive music *
Ready?
Fuck yeah.
On three. One, two, three.
[car engines revving over TV]
-Police! Show me your hands!
-Get your fucking hands up!
Hands up! Hands up!
-Nice. Very credible.
Oh, yeah, you like that, huh?
Get on your fucking knees!
Don't you fucking move.
Get on your fucking knees.
No Shirt, get your
fucking hands up!
And on your knees!
-Zip-tie 'em!
-Don't move.
-Tyson?
It-It's Ben. We--
Criminology 101, freshman year?
Fuck, you're a cop now?
Bitch, get the fuck up.
Get the fuck up!
Where the contraband at?
Huh?!
* upbeat, percussive music *
[Goodie whistles softly]
-Very good.
-This all of it, huh?
-Everything?
-That's it.
I'm glad we went
to school together, man.
I'm-a spare your ass today.
You ain't going into jail.
What-- Are we, like,
under arrest?
You didn't read us our rights
or anything.
Listen up, fuck-face.
You don't want to end up
in jail.
Your skinny ass will get reamed
on day one.
Hey, maybe we can come up with
-some type of agreement.
-Let's go, let's go.
You know, keep you and your boys
out of the system, huh?
* playful music *
[engine starts]
[tires squealing]
We good, we good.
We good.
-What's my cut?
-Already?
Look, I appreciate the moxie,
but, uh, that's not
how this works.
This is, like, a thousand hits.
Yo, Spence,
what's-what's the name
of the bar you work at again?
-Is it Spit?
-Sweat.
-Spit. That's right.
-You're gonna work up a sweat
-selling all that.
-Great.
But what's my finder's fee?
Relax. We'll work something out.
All right, look.
I'm taking 50% of the cash.
The pills-- that's you two.
I want nothing to do with it.
Dwight'll take me apart
if he ever found out.
Hey, Spence, I need to know:
can you really sell
this shit fast?
I know every bartender
and DJ in the city.
Every club and rave.
I can sell this shit
in ten minutes.
-All right.
-But I want 50% of the gross.
-That's how it works.
-Hey.
50 per-- What kind of business
classes is you taking?
["Call Me the Breeze"
by Lynyrd Skynyrd playing]
Wait in the car, Kyle.
***
* Call me the breeze *
[croupier]
Pot nine. Winner nine.
* I keep blowin'
down the road... *
[excited chatter]
Here he comes.
Okay. Bye.
So glad you could make it.
When you get a call
from a storied Oklahoma family
like the Threshers,
the only reply is,
"Where and what time?"
Well, thank you
for indulging me.
Now, I don't question the meet.
I question the location.
Well, our campaign is
hitting its stride,
and I think a lot of that
is because
I've been rubbing shoulders
with real Oklahomans.
Fine folk like these.
[waitress]
Gentlemen.
Something from the bar?
[Sackrider]
I will take
-an Arnold Palmer, please.
-[waitress] Mm-hmm.
Grey Goose martini with a twist.
[stammering] Make it two.
Coming right up.
Hope I'm not pulling you
over to the dark side.
Nah, a little day drinking
never hurt anybody.
[patrons cheering,
chattering excitedly]
***
[muffled music playing]
[Thresher]
Mm.
You know, I've been
watching your career
with admiration.
[Sackrider]
Really? I had no idea.
[Thresher]
Oh, sure.
I mean, what you did
with those gang members
in Oklahoma City,
that was some old-school
justice,
meted out with a firm hand.
All in service of
the good people of Oklahoma.
Oh, well, amen to that.
***
I've been putting a lot
of money behind this campaign.
I intend to win.
Grace.
[Thresher]
Mm-mm.
It's about having the power
to get things done.
[Mitch]
Easy does it.
[Thresher]
...affect real change.
That's why I want you
on our team.
Jump wagon. Come on.
Why not reap the benefits
of my PAC's contributions?
And all you have to do in return
-is to endorse me.
-Look, I'm...
I'm flattered and honored,
but no.
[Dwight] If he's any closer,
he'd be in his DNA.
-[Thresher] ...change your mind?
-[Sackrider] I am not one...
[Mitch]
There she goes.
We don't usually get
such esteemed guests
here at the Bred-2-Buck.
The owners would like to extend
this courtesy,
in case you'd like to enjoy
-any of our gaming options.
-Wow.
Well, uh, thank you, young lady.
[quietly]
You son of a bitch.
-Come on, Cal.
-Oh, no, no. No.
No, not you. I was thinking
of somebody else.
You know what?
-Let's just change the subject.
-[Margaret] Nice.
[Sackrider] Why not just
spend the house's money,
call it a day?
No hard feelings.
None whatsoever.
[Dwight]
Unbelievable.
-[door opens]
-[indistinct chatter]
[door closes]
-Amazing Grace.
-[giggles]
[Thresher] Now, now, now,
don't forget this.
[Sackrider]
Oh. Yes, sir.
-[Dwight chuckles]
-[Margaret] There we go.
[Dwight]
Hook, line and sinker.
He's like a wind-up toy.
Shit.
Is that who I think it is?
[Dwight]
Yeah.
Let's go.
Nah, I'll take care of this.
I got it.
You sure?
He's got his people with him.
Yeah, I know.
But he won't do anything here.
Bigfoot.
[Jeremiah]
Ah, look at these guys.
[birds singing]
You guys lost?
You pay a visit
to my attorney general,
you think
he's not gonna call me?
I expected that.
[Jeremiah]
So you're trying to bait me.
Raise my ire.
[Dwight] You know
there's an ancient book
called The Art of War?
It's a military theses
that was written in
the fifth or sixth century BC.
I'm sure you're not familiar
with it.
Any of you guys?
What's that got to do
with a goddamn thing?
[Dwight] It's got
everything to do with it,
because it's
all about your enemy:
learning about them, their
strengths, their weaknesses.
But it also says,
"Build your fucking enemy
a golden bridge
so they can escape
and save face."
[Jeremiah]
You want an off-ramp, Manfredi?
Ask for it.
I built you a bridge, Dunmire.
Use it.
The balls on you.
You got no way
to distill or distribute,
and you won't have one.
I control the law.
[Dwight]
And the governor.
For now.
You know, the thing
about people...
[snaps fingers]
...they change overnight.
People don't change.
And if they do, well...
You stay away from my people.
Or I'll bury you next.
Mm.
Use the bridge, Dunmire.
[Jeremiah laughs]
[footsteps receding]
[car doors open and close]
[rock music playing]
-Hey!
-Hard eight!
Oh, yeah, baby. Hard eights.
That'll play.
I'll take eights all night long.
So what's your long-term plan?
Oh...
to make... [chuckles]
...some money.
Professionally.
I'll be looking for
a lieutenant governor
that I can trust.
Wow. You're pretty handy
around these tables.
[exhales] Don't tell my wife.
Oh...
I'm pretty good
at keeping a secret.
-Yes, sir!
-[whooping, laughter]
-[muffled music playing]
-[muffled chatter]
[Dwight]
I like to gamble.
-But not with money.
-Mm.
Mm, you gamble on people.
I do.
I try to figure out
their next move.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
Do you know what my next move
-is gonna be?
-Yeah, of course.
"Of course"?
We got to stay focused, okay?
What? I am!
What did you mean?
Well, you're pretty obvious,
-let's face it.
-Oh--
Grace.
'Bout time to change his luck.
* lively, upbeat music *
[patrons cheering]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[Sackrider] Holy shit.
We are on a roll, Cal.
Hey. You know, you, uh...
you might want to quit
while you're ahead.
No, I'm playing
with the house's money.
Dealer.
There's no downside here.
Shit. Well...
-Yeah. Shit.
-[Sackrider] Yeah.
Can't win 'em all.
All right.
Let's come back out.
Two crap, crap dice.
Oh, boy.
-Look, you know, maybe--
-Don't change the mood, Cal.
[slams chips on table]
Show me some midnight.
Show me some...
Colt .45, anything...
anything, anything but Big Red.
[patrons groan]
-Son of a... bitch!
-Three, crap dice.
Unbelievable.
-[patrons groan]
-Oh...
Three, crap three.
That's crap dice.
Mr. Sackrider, based on
your standing in the community,
you're preapproved for 100,000.
What?
[rock music playing]
Then I guess I have...
-have some pull around here.
-Somebody does.
How much of that
line of credit would you
-like to draw from, sir?
-Uh... [whimpers softly]
Um...
[laughs] All-all of it.
[Thresher]
Ooh.
[Sackrider]
Let's go, people.
Shit is about to get real!
Aw, shit.
Ooh, un-fucking-believable.
Now this guy's gonna blame me.
He's a gambler, Cal.
Can't blame you for his vice.
Listen, he wouldn't have
come here for me.
He just needed a nudge from you.
A nudge?
Have you been
in on this the whole time?
Mm, I had a little intel
from his wife, so... yeah.
Look, Governor, I'm gonna
have him in my pocket.
That means he's gonna be
in yours.
[Margaret]
Win-win.
Don't ever play me
like this again.
Either of you.
Is this gonna be a problem
with this guy?
-He'll cool down.
-Mm, yeah.
Fucking neurotic.
Try Xanax.
-[birds chirping]
-[chickens clucking]
[liquid running]
[Cole]
Trying to call you.
Course.
Can I ask you something?
I'm genuinely curious.
Why do you fail so much?
* ominous music *
I do what you ask.
If success were
the broad side of a barn,
you couldn't hit it
with a 12-gauge shotgun.
Seriously...
[cork squeaks]
...did your mama hit you
on the head
when you were growing up, or is
there something else going on?
Maybe you just want
to embarrass or...
sabotage the family legacy.
The family legacy?
I'm it.
I'm all that's left
of this family once you go.
But you care more
about this stuff you brew
than your own son.
Maybe you're just
a jumped-up wannabe
that plays at tough.
Unless those muscles are
covering up for a goddamn...
...defective soul.
Is that it?
You fucked up in Hot Springs.
The good,
they really do die young.
* It don't care
where you stand *
["Below the Waterline"
by Jason Eady playing]
* 'Cause when
the river is rising *
* It's gonna take everything *
* Below the waterline *
Drinks are on the house.
* Well, people are runnin'
and people are fightin'... *
What are you doing here?
Adding.
You owe the house
a hundred large.
I am the house.
* Countin' on luck... *
I thought this was
a Native American place.
It is. I just run operations.
* It don't care what you think *
* It don't care
where you stand... *
Were those dice loaded?
The only thing loaded is you.
* It's gonna take everything *
* Below the waterline *
I don't have that kind of money.
[Sackrider sniffles]
You know what?
I'm willing to waive the debt.
* The city is sinking
an inch at a time... *
What's...
what's the catch?
[Dwight]
The catch is this:
you let me protect you
from people that will kick you
when you're down and out.
[sniffles]
I've got your back.
If...
you've got mine.
-[inhales sharply]
-[song ends]
[door opens]
Package arrived for you, sir.
Is it ticking?
No.
These are the jokes, dear.
[weak chuckle]
[letter opener clatters on desk]
* tense music *
***
Let me call you back.
Hey, Jeremiah.
Have-have a seat.
You restored Manfredi's license.
That was a... tragic accident,
Jeremiah, an accident.
Distillery was cleared.
There's no cause
to keep it shuttered.
There's always a cause.
There's always a cause
when I call for a goddamn one.
What's he paying you?
-What's he paying you?
-Not a penny.
He's right about one thing.
Hacks like you are
always for sale.
You're already in his pocket.
I only serve
the good people of Oklahoma.
You only serve me.
You serve me!
Well...
I have stronger protectors now
than you, Jeremiah.
Men of honor.
What did you say?
Dwight Manfredi has a code
that you lack.
[screaming]
-You motherf--
-[screaming]
Help! Security!
Squeal!
Squeal like the pig you are!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[grunts]
Ow!
* tense music *
[indistinct, distant shouting]
Sorry about this, Mr. Dunmire.
I'm just doing my job.
Don't give it a second thought.
I believe setbacks
are necessary.
They give one perspective.
And a chance to see the road
to redemption with clearer eyes.
[buzzing]
[outer door shuts]
***
* percussive, upbeat music *